Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Caught off Guard
Episode 10
Do you think we can really defeat that monster?
Don’t worry I found a way
When I return to the city, I will tame that monster with everyone.
The king is so majestic
Still have to rely on Father
The king is so powerful
Your Majesty
Father, Father
you’re going in the wrong direction
Your Highness, Your Highness, Your Highness
Your Highness, where are you? Where are you?
Where are you? He shouldn’t have gone into the forest, right?
Your Highness
that is
Found His Highness Prince Sparky
it’s him
Did I read that right?
The one in front of His Highness seems to be His Majesty
is true
His Majesty is alive
Really? I want to see it too
His Majesty
This trip is truly a double blessing, Master Quan
Then why don’t you hurry up and greet them?
obey
Finally came out
Welcome His Majesty
Your Majesty, it’s great that Your Majesty is okay.
when Your Majesty was not around
Monsters were always harassing us and grabbing our Bulala
The Bulala Kingdom cannot live without Your Majesty.
Everyone has been wronged
Don’t worry
This time I come back and I will definitely solve the monster problem
Your Majesty
It is that monster
Why did it suddenly come here?
The monster you are talking about
It turns out it is
It turns out to be so cute
It was too dark to see clearly before
Do you know this monster?
Don’t be afraid, everyone, soldiers listen to my orders
Your Majesty, take care of yourself
Father
Little Cutie, look over here
that is
Welcome to grassland craft class
Let us teach you how to make a toy stick in one second
Just need a rope
and my bell
Weslie and Wolffy’s special toy stick completed
learned
No Little Cutie can say no to this
The monster seems to have become docile
Why did it suddenly get angry again?
Run away
Why do I feel like this monster is targeting me?
Father, run quickly
Let’s use the same rhythm of cooperation we used on the mountain to control the monster together.
Everyone come together
I’ll come
Shrink
Is this monster because you have beaten it before, Father
So it came here specifically to take revenge on you?
I think it’s not that simple
What
What happened just now?
His Majesty is right. It may not be that simple.
Weslie what are you going to do
Don’t go near it alone
Sure enough, there is transparent wool controlling the Little Cutie
Maybe after we cut that thread
The monster will return to normal
Leave it to me to cut the line
Saw it
You continue
let me
Wolffy, give me a helping hand
final blow
Father
Don’t be afraid. It’s okay now.
Your Majesty. Father
It’s okay, it’s okay
Finally solved the monster problem
But what’s going on with this line?
Who was controlling the Little Cutie?
let me take a look
This kind of line
I know you are nearby
Come out, Brother
Brother
It was actually discovered
No wonder, it’s you
You were afraid that the thread would be revealed, so you ran away at that time.
Uncle, why would you do such a thing?
I believe you won’t do this
Do you have any difficulties?
How could you understand
what I did
is just to
take back what belongs to me
This powerful energy
How could Uncle become so powerful?
The power gap is too big. Let’s escape first and then talk about it.
Don’t even think about escaping
Father
Run quickly
Why why are you doing this?
Sparky
To be continued